Finding Aid for francisco
Clarke Historical Library
- Francisco Photography Studio Photographic Collection is open for research.
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Couple with Baby,undated (Box 4, Folder 598)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Female Graduate,undated (Box 4, Folder 599)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Girl,undated (Box 4, Folder 600)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Little Girl,undated (Box 4, Folder 601)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Little Girl,1930 (Box 4, Folder 602)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Man,undated (Box 4, Folder 603)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Man Fishing,1930 (Box 4, Folder 604)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Man Playing Piano,undated (Box 4, Folder 605)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Older Couple,undated (Box 4, Folder 606)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Patient with a Doctor,undated (Box 4, Folder 607)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Teenager,undated (Box 4, Folder 608)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Woman,undated (Box 4, Folder 609)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Woman,1930 (Box 4, Folder 610)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Woman Carrying a Little Girl,1930 (Box 4, Folder 611)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Woman Ice Skating,undated (Box 4, Folder 612)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Woman with a Girl,undated (Box 4, Folder 613)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Young Woman,undated (Box 4, Folder 614)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Chief Shooting Bull,undated (Box 4, Folder 615)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Cross Village,August 24, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 616)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Dog,undated (Box 4, Folder 617)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Downtown,undated (Box 4, Folder 618)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Estates,1930 (Box 4, Folder 619)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Five Little Children,undated (Box 4, Folder 620)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Five People,undated (Box 4, Folder 621)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Four Little Boys,undated (Box 4, Folder 622)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Glen's First Cooking Class,undated (Box 4, Folder 623)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Hospital with Army Soldiers and Nurses,undated (Box 4, Folder 624)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Houghton Lake,March 24, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 625)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Party,undated (Box 4, Folder 626)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Older Woman in the Living Room,undated (Box 4, Folder 627)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Negative of 6 family members seated,undated (Box 4, Folder 628)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Studio,undated (Box 4, Folder 629)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Three Older Men,undated (Box 4, Folder 630)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Three Women,undated (Box 4, Folder 631)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Two Girls,undated (Box 4, Folder 632)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Two Little Girls,undated (Box 4, Folder 633)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Two Men,undated (Box 4, Folder 634)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco Family - Two Men Boxing,undated (Box 4, Folder 635)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco, H.A.,undated (Box 4, Folder 636)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Francisco, Lillian and Harrison - Copy of Each One's Driver's License,undated (Box 4, Folder 637)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Frank, Carl,undated (Box 4, Folder 638)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Frank, Linda - Girl,undated (Box 4, Folder 639)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Frank, Ray - I.D.,undated (Box 4, Folder 640)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Franklin, Wm. and Wife,May 6, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 641)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Franko, Joe A. (p.p.),June 27, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 642)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Frantz, June,undated (Box 4, Folder 643)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Frantz, June - 5- and 2-year-old Girls,undated (Box 4, Folder 644)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Frantz, Wm. and Wife,September 27,1 969 (Box 4, Folder 645)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Frederick, Richard,November 29, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 646)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Freeman, Alden - Wedding,undated (Box 4, Folder 647)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Frees, Jerome,undated (Box 4, Folder 648)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Freeze, Barbara,undated (Box 4, Folder 649)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Freeze, Pearl - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 650)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Frick, August, Sr. - Family Photograph,undated (Box 4, Folder 651)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Frick, August, Sr. and Wife,undated (Box 4, Folder 652)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Frick, Carl (2 envelopes),undated (Box 4, Folder 653)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Frick, Carl - Baby,undated (Box 4, Folder 654)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Frick, Carl - 8-month-old,undated (Box 4, Folder 655)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Frick, Carl,April 25, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 656)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Frick, Frank - Baby,undated (Box 4, Folder 657)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Frick, Frank - Baby Girl,1955 (Box 4, Folder 658)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Frick, Frank - Little Girl,1959 (Box 4, Folder 659)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Frick, Max,undated (Box 4, Folder 660)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Frick, Otto,undated (Box 4, Folder 661)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Frissman, Mrs. Walt - 1-year-old Girl,undated (Box 4, Folder 662)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Froggett, Nelson - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 663)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fuentes, Virginia,undated (Box 4, Folder 664)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fulk, Chas.,undated (Box 4, Folder 665)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Funnell, Edna - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 667)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Funnell, Jerry,undated (Box 4, Folder 668)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Funnell, Jerry and Wife - Passport,February 6, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 669)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Funnell, Joyce,undated (Box 4, Folder 670)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fussman, Jack,undated (Box 4, Folder 671)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Fussman, John,undated (Box 4, Folder 672)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Galgoczi, Steve - Moose Lodge Gov.,December 9, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 673)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gallardo, Raymond - Wedding,undated (Box 4, Folder 674)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gamary, Matt,undated (Box 4, Folder 675)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gamble's Store,undated (Box 4, Folder 676)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Garber, Wanda,undated (Box 4, Folder 677)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Garchow, Amy,undated (Box 4, Folder 678)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gardner, Veronica,undated (Box 4, Folder 679)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Garner, Bob,undated (Box 4, Folder 680)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Garrett, Carol,undated (Box 4, Folder 681)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Garthy, Anne,undated (Box 4, Folder 682)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gatcher, [no first name],undated (Box 4, Folder 683)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gatehouse, Gary - 6- and 8-month-olds,August 24, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 684)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gatehouse, Ruth - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 685)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gates, Earl - Copy of Family Photograph,undated (Box 4, Folder 686)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gates, Ivan - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 687)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gates, Shirley,undated (Box 4, Folder 688)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gaudard, Max,undated (Box 4, Folder 689)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Geasler, Carl,July 7, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 690)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Geasler, Joan,undated (Box 4, Folder 691)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Geasler, Myritle,undated (Box 4, Folder 692)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gelander, Harry,undated (Box 4, Folder 693)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Genson, Clifford,undated (Box 4, Folder 694)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gepford, Bill - 9-month-old,undated (Box 4, Folder 695)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gepford, Pat - 9-month-old,undated (Box 4, Folder 696)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gepford, Pat - 10-month-old,1961 (Box 4, Folder 697)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gepford, Pat - 7-month-old,undated (Box 4, Folder 698)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gerve, Ruth,March 10, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 699)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Getchell, Bud and Wife,undated (Box 4, Folder 700)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Getchell, Evelyn,undated (Box 4, Folder 701)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Getchell, Jane, Mrs.,undated (Box 4, Folder 702)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Getchell, John, H.S.,undated (Box 4, Folder 703)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Getchell, Lois - 7-month-old,undated (Box 4, Folder 704)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Getchell, Pat,undated (Box 4, Folder 705)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gibson, Alva -10-year-old Boy,undated (Box 4, Folder 706)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gibson, Dorothy,undated (Box 4, Folder 707)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gibson, Jane - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 708)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gibson, Jerry,undated (Box 4, Folder 709)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gibson, Marge,undated (Box 4, Folder 710)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gibson, Marie,July 10, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 711)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gibson, Rita,undated (Box 4, Folder 712)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gibson, Sadie,undated (Box 4, Folder 713)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gibson, Steve,undated (Box 4, Folder 714)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gibson, Wilard, Jr. - 7-month-old Marie,undated (Box 4, Folder 715)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gilchrist, Gordon - 1.5-year-old,undated (Box 4, Folder 716)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gill, Louise,undated (Box 4, Folder 717)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gill, Terry,undated (Box 4, Folder 718)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gillian, Mary,undated (Box 4, Folder 719)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gillet, Eileen,undated (Box 4, Folder 720)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gillet, Eileen Rose - Birth Certificate,undated (Box 4, Folder 721)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gillette, Dory and Wife - Copy,January 3, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 722)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gillette, Jesse, Mrs.,undated (Box 4, Folder 723)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gillhooley, Ed,undated (Box 4, Folder 724)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gillis, Don and Wife - Son and Daughter,July 14, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 725)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gillis, Sharon,undated (Box 4, Folder 726)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gillis, Stan,undated (Box 4, Folder 728)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gilmore, Maynard,undated (Box 4, Folder 729)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gilmore, Nelda,undated (Box 4, Folder 730)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gilpin, Brenda,undated (Box 4, Folder 731)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Glover, Susan,undated (Box 4, Folder 732)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Goodrich, Marion,undated (Box 4, Folder 733)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gott, John - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 734)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Goudie, Nancy,undated (Box 4, Folder 735)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gover, Bob - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 736)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gover, N.D.,April 29, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 737)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gover, N.D. - Dog,undated (Box 4, Folder 738)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gover, N.D. - Family,undated (Box 4, Folder 739)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gover, N.D. and Wife,undated (Box 4, Folder 740)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gover, Harry and Wife,undated (Box 4, Folder 741)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Gover, Robert,undated (Box 4, Folder 742)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Grace, Dick,undated (Box 4, Folder 743)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Grace, Floyd, Mrs.,undated (Box 4, Folder 744)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Grace, Karen,August 18, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 745)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Grace, Lonnie,March 22, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 746)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Grace, Richard,undated (Box 4, Folder 747)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Grace, Zeke, Mrs. - Copy,undated (Box 4, Folder 748)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Graham, Bob,undated (Box 4, Folder 749)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Graham, Henry, Mrs.,undated (Box 4, Folder 750)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Graham, Jackie,undated (Box 4, Folder 751)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Graham, Lowell,undated (Box 4, Folder 752)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Graham, Ronald - Birth Certificate,undated (Box 4, Folder 753)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Graham, Ronald - Honorable Discharge,undated (Box 4, Folder 754)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Grandy, Jean,undated (Box 4, Folder 755)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, A-Gran, Granger, L.E.,October 15, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 756)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Graves, Pauline,undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Gray, Arlene,undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Gray, Natalie,undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Gregg, Lewis,undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Gregg, Norma,undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Grenada, H.,undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Grewe, Ruth,undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Griffin, L. - G.I. and Sister,undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Griffin, Tom,undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Griffith, Stephen,undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Grinstern, Patty,undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Grisdale, Art - Family,undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Grisdale, Betty,undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Griswold, H.,undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Grodski, Gertrude,undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Gross, Bernard - 1- and 2-year-olds,January 4, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Gross, Betty,undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Gross, Bob,undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Gross, Claire,undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Gross, Donald J.,undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Gross, Ernest,undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Gross, Esther,undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Gross, Marilyn (2 envelopes),undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Gross, Theresa,undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Gross, Wm. - Baby Girl,undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Grove, Albert (2),March 8, August 16, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Grove, Barbara,undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Grove, Miles,undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Grove, Tom,undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Groves, Alice,undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Grubb, Robert - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Gruss, Joe,undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Gruss, Joe - Family Photograph,1962 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Gruss, Marie - 1-year-old,undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Gruss, Peter,March 6, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Guest, G. - Baby,undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Gullett, Don,undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Gundel, Mrs. - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Gunton, Morlba,undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Guthrie, Mrs.and Mr. - Son - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Guthrie, Howard,March 6, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Haas, Geo.,May 6, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hackett, Elaine,,undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hackett, John and Wife (2 envelopes),undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hackett, K.,undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hackett, Rose,undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hadlock, Mary - 7-month-old,undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hafer, Charol - 9-year-old,undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hafer, Julie Ann,February 11, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hafer, Pamela,undated (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hagerman, Geo.,undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Haggart, Joyce,undated (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Haggart, Robert,undated (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Haggart, Virgul,undated (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hall, Carol,undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hall, Clarence,undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hall, Curtiss,undated (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hall, Jerry -15-month-old,undated (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hall, Lonna,undated (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hall, Ray, Mrs.,undated (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hall, Stanley - 2-year-old,undated (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hall, Tink - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hall, Wayne,undated (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hallock, Harold and Wife,undated (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Halton, Jackie,undated (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hamilton, Fred,undated (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hammel, Arnold - Photograph,undated (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hammond, Ann - 2-year-old,undated (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hammond, Glenn, Mrs. - Sailor,September 18, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Haney, Arnold - Leo Scramlin,undated (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hanlin, H. - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Haring, Fred,undated (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Harless, Harold,undated (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Harless, Kay,undated (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Harless, Pauline,undated (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Harless, Roy - Policeman,undated (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Harless, Ruth, Mrs. - Couple,undated (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Harper, Elmer - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Harris, Donna - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Harris, John,undated (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Harris, Phil,undated (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Harrison, Chas.,undated (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Harrison,J.E.,,May 3, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hart, Clara - 5-year-old,undated (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hart, Shirley,undated (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hartman, Darwin,July 7, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Harvey, [no first name],undated (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Haskins, Shirley,undated (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hatt, F.,undated (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hatt, Lavier -8-year-old Girl,undated (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hatt, Lillian, Mrs. - Boy,undated (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hauck, Floyd - 9-month-old,June 23, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Haught, Colleen - I.D.,July 7, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hause, Ed - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hawkins, Burton,January 3, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hawkins, Jerry,undated (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Haynes, Cathy,undated (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Haynes, Judy,undated (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Haynes, Leo,undated (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Haynes, Patty - Girl,undated (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hazelton, Duane,undated (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hazelton, Esther,undated (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Hazelton, Mary Lou,undated (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Heckert, Jim,September 12, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Heckler, Ted,October 25, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Heinlein, Dan,undated (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Heinlein, Robt.,undated (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Heinlein, Sandy - Copy,undated (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Heinlein, Wm.,undated (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Heintman, Eric C.,undated (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Heintz, Robert,undated (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Henry, V.,undated (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Henshaw, Joe - 2-year-old,undated (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, Grav-R, Heppler, John,July 3, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 114)